Lukasz Pietraszek

Mid-weight UI/Front-end developer

PERSONAL SUMMARY

UI/Front-end developer with proven track-record over five years in creating accessible and user-friendly responsive websites. Self motivated and independent minded, with a keen eye for detail. Two months of commercial use of AngularJS (2 months) on B2B project. Experienced in working with Hybris CMS and Agile methodologies.

Specialities: HTML5, CSS3, Web Design/Development, RWD, Usability, Web Standards, Axure RP, Hybris CMS

WORK EXPERIENCE

Front-end Developer

September 2015 — present

Sceneric, London // www.sceneric.com

Integrating front-end prototype with Hybris CMS for Gucci's new e-commerce website

Front-end Developer

August 2015

Jack Wills, London // www.jackwills.com

Maintaining and bug fixing main website. Tech stack: Demandware CMS, RequireJS, HTML, LESS

UI Developer

August 2013 — August 2015

Portaltech Reply, London // www.portaltech.co.uk

Developing and integrating front-end with Hybris[y] CMS for number of e-commerce websites using HTML5, CSS3, Less/SASS, Bootstrap 3, jQuery and AngularJS Clients: Phones4U, Monsoon Accessorize, OFFICE, BAT, Delhaize

Front-end Developer

May 2011 — August 2013

BioMed Central, London // www.biomedcentral.com

Designing layouts and front end structure for three main portals and tens of independent journals. Responsible for developing WordPress themes for blogs using responsive web design with HTML5 and CSS3.

Web and Graphic Designer

November 2007 — May 2011

Ascent IT Ltd, London // www.hueanimation.com

Designing and maintaining three main websites www.hueanimation.com, www.huehd.com and www.sogatel.com

Front-end Developer

August 2005 — May 2011

Looca Design, London // looca.co.uk

Freelance front-end developer. For several years I have been creating website for commerce, charities and artists.

EDUCATION

ABC Level 3 Certificate in Digital Graphics

Sept 2008 — Aug 2009

London College of Communication, Elephant & Castle, London

BSc Computer Science with Business Management Sept 2002 — Jun 2005

The University of Management and Marketing, Sosnowiec, Poland

A-Levels (Polish, Mathematics, Geography)

Sept 1998 — Jun 2002

Electronics and Informatics High School, Sosnowiec, Poland

E: pietraszek@hotmail.co.uk

W: looca.co.uk

L: linkedin.com/in/pietraszekl

T: twitter.com/pietraszekl

SKILLS

HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, jQuery, AngularJS, Sass, Less, UX, Responsive Web Design, Web Standards, Usability

TOOLS

Hybris [y] CMS, Wordpress, Eclipse, GIT, SVN, GruntJS, Axure RP, Photoshop, Illustrator

WORK EXAMPLES

www.ab.gr shop.delhaize.be www.poferries.com uk.monsoon.co.uk biomedcentral.com/biome BMC Research Awards beyond-the-genome.com elenabudnikova.com hueanimation.com

CLIENTS

Gucci

Delhaize Group

Phones₄U

Office Shoes

Costco

Monsoon/Accessorize British American Tobacco

Cukasz is a great addition to our UI team at Portaltech Reply. He is a 'go-to' person when you need a quick and complete solution. Technical and with a keen eye for detail, Lukasz also has the rare quality of genuine self drive which has displayed itself whilst being UI project lead for one of our largest global clients.

Simon Davies

Head of UX at Portaltech Reply